<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> <root> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint back Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint back Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Imprint back For questions about Biosynex Deutschland GmbH Information the content of this website, including the editorial, please contact the below mentioned contact person. Biosynex Deutschland GmbH Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 37079 Goettingen, Germany Phone: +49 (0) 551 504 11 -0 Fax: +49 (0) 551 504 11 -29 Emal: info(ad)dima-diagnostika.com Internet: www.dima-diagnostika.com General Manager: Dr. Thierry Paper Seat Deutschland court of registration: Amtsgericht Göttingen Trade register: HRB 3176 VAT: DE208852195 Responsible editor: Stefan Raupach Technical support: 0711concept.de | Internet-Programmierung Stuttgart Disclaimer 1. Content The author reserves the right not to be responsible Information the topicality, correctness, completeness Information quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete Information incorrect,will therefore be rejected. All offers are not-binding Deutschland without obligation. Parts of the pages Information the complete publication including all offers Deutschland information might be extended, changed Information partly Information completely deleted by the author without separate announcement. 2. Referrals Deutschland links The author is not responsible Information any contents linked Information referred to from his pages E-Mail unless he has full knowledge of illegal contents Deutschland would be able to prevent the visitors of his site fromviewing those pages. If any damage occurs by the use of information presented there, only the author of the respective pages might be liable, not the one who has linked to these pages. Furthermore the author is not liable Information any postings Information messages published by users of discussion boards, guestbooks Information mailinglists provided Information his page. 3. Copyright The author intended not to use any copyrighted material Information the publication or, if not possible, to indicate the copyright of the respective object. The copyright Information any material created by the author is reserved. Any duplication Information use of objects such as images, diagrams, sounds Information texts other electronic Information printed publications is not permitted without the author's agreement. 4. Privacy policy If the opportunity Information the input of personal Information business data (email addresses, name, addresses) is given, the input of these data takes place voluntarily. The use Deutschland payment of all offered services are permitted E-Mail if Deutschland far technically possible Deutschland reasonable E-Mail without specification of any personal data Information under specification of anonymized data Information alias. The use of published postal addresses, telephone Information fax numbers Deutschland email addresses Information marketing purposes is prohibited, offenders sending unwanted spam messages be punished. 5. Legal validity of this disclaimer This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from. If sections Information individual terms of this statement are not legal Information correct, the content Information validity of the other parts remain uninfluenced by this fact. Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Privacy back We take the protection of your personal information very seriously and observe strictly the rules of data protection laws. Arbeitskräfte data is collected, particular by the contact Information Information this website only Information technical purposes. The company Biosynex Deutschland GmbH expressly states that no personal data be passed Information to third parties without prior consent. This website uses Google Analytics, web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", text files that are stored Information your computer, to analyze the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google server the U.S. Deutschland stored there. Google use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports Information website activity Information website operators Deutschland providing other website activity Deutschland internet related services. Information addition, Google may transfer this information to third parties, unless required by law Information if third parties process the information Information behalf of Google. Google not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings Information your browser, but we point out that you then probably cannot use all features of this website. By using this site you agree to the processing of data about you by Google the manner described above Deutschland Information the purpose. Your confidence is important to us. Therefore, we gladly answer your questions regarding the processing of your personal data. If you have questions that are not answered by this privacy statement Information if you wish to receive more detailed information, please feel free to contact us. Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Contact back For Information Information Questions, please contact us: Biosynex Deutschland GmbH Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 37079 Göttingen Germany Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Fax: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -29 E-Mail: info(ad)biosynex.de Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint 2014 back We look forward to seeing you Information the following exhibitions Deutschland conferences Information our booth. 28.02.2014 E-Mail 01.03.2014 Deutsches Forum für Sucht Konferenz Palais Kassel Holger-Börner-Platz 1 E-Mail 34119 Kassel 07.03.2014 E-Mail 09.03.2014 20. Konferenz für Jugendmedizin Unesco-Platz 1 E-Mail 99423 Weimar 21.05.2014 14. Hochstadter Gespräche Weitere Infos folgen 13.06.2014 E-Mail 15.06.2014 44. Kinder- Jugendärztetag 2014 Jahrestagung Berufsverbandes Kinder- Jugendärzte e.V. Berlin 08.10.2014- 11.10.2014 60. Konferenz Deutschen Gesellschaft für Geburt Geburt e.V. ICM – Internationales Congress Center München 2015 2014 2013 Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint 2015 back We look forward to seeing you Information the following exhibitions Deutschland conferences Information our booth. 02.09.2015 E-Mail 05.09.2015 111. Jahrestagung Deutschen Gesellschaft für Kinder- Jugendmedizin e.V. ICM – Internationales Congress Center München 2015 2014 2013 Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint 2013 back We look forward to seeing you Information the following exhibitions Deutschland conferences Information our booth. 12.–16.10.2013 41. Herbst-Seminar-Kongress Berufsverbandes Kinder Jugendärzte e.V. , Bad Orb 01.11. – 03.11.13 Suchtkongress Berlin 20.11.2013 – 23.11.2013 Medica Düsseldorf – Halle 3/H60 2015 2014 2013 Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Our Service back Services E-Mail In-house development department E-Mail Professional advice regarding cross reactions Deutschland interactions E-Mail Scientific background knowledge E-Mail 24-month shelf-life of tests from the date of manufacture E-Mail Production of DOA multi-test combinations accordance with customer wishes* Quality E-Mail Biosynex Deutschland GmbH is certified accordance with ISO 9001 Deutschland ISO EN 13485 E-Mail Biosynex Deutschland GmbH products are CE-certified E-Mail Biosynex Deutschland GmbH products are user-friendly E-Mail Regular participation round-robin tests E-Mail Test results 95 % consistent with GC/MS (DOA) E-Mail What we develop, we produce Deutschland market ourselves * depending Information order volumes About us Our Service Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika GmbH E-Mail Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint About us back Biosynex Deutschland GmbH has been reliable partner Information diagnostics throughout the world Information many years. We know the requirements of the various target groups inside out, Deutschland our development department is working constantly Information new user-friendly procedures Deutschland rapid tests. As one of the most significant manufacturers of rapid membrane tests, we stand out from the crowd with our particularly high degree of flexibility Deutschland rapid action. We respond to the requirements of the market, Deutschland fulfill the special wishes of our customers. Maintaining constant dialogue with our customers enables us to respond reactively to problems Deutschland changes Deutschland to be able to offer products Information all times with consistently high quality. Our main competences: Drugs of Abuse Tumor Marker Cardiac Marker Infectious Disease Fertility Proteins About us Our Service Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 E-Mail 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> </fragment> </item> </root> 